Sound Recordings of Museum-Related Events
The Museum of Modern Art, Publisher
- General Sound Recordings of Museum-Related Activities, 1939-present
  - "What's so Funny?", February 12, 1991; PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art. SERIES: New York Women in Film, "What's so Funny?" PARTICIPANTS:Mary Lea Bandy, Director of Department of Film, The Museum of Modern Art; Molly Haskell, critic; Madeline Kahn, actress. DATA: 2 90 Minute Standard Audio Cassettes. SUMMARY: Molly Haskell speaks about the "blonde bombshell" followed by Madeline Kahn who shows footage of her own work. The two then discuss the role of women in film. RELATED MATERIAL: 2000.160a, 2000.106b. DONOR: Department of Film TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: Spring 2000 (Item 2000.105b)
  - "What's so Funny?", January 22, 1991; SERIES: New York Women in Film, "What's so Funny?" PARTICIPANTS: Mary Lea Bandy, Director of Department of Film, The Museum of Modern Art; Nora Ephron, film director; Wendy Wasserstein, playwright. SUMMARY: Mary Lea Bandy explores comedic scriptwriting and film. Participants follow and answer questions from the audience. DATA: 2 90 Minute Standard Audio Cassettes. DONOR: Department of Film. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: Spring 2000; NOTE: Recording periodically slows (Item 2000.106a)
  - "What's so Funny?", January 22, 1991; SERIES: New York Women in Film, "What's so Funny?" PARTICIPANTS: Mary Lea Bandy, Director of Department of Film, The Museum of Modern Art; Nora Ephron, film director; Wendy Wasserstein, playwright. SUMMARY: Mary Lea Bandy explores comedic scriptwriting and film. Participants follow and answer questions from the audience. DATA: 2 90 Minute Standard Audio Cassettes. DONOR: Department of Film. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: Spring 2000; NOTE: Recording periodically slows (Item 2000.106b)
  - "What's So Funny?", January 29, 1991; SERIES: "What's So Funny?" PARTICIPANTS: Charles Silver, curator, Department of Film; Elizabeth Kendall, critic. SPONSOR: New York Women in Film SUMMARY: Charles Silver speaks about comedic strategies in the 1920's and 1930's. DATA: 2 90 Minute Standard Audio Cassettes. RELATED MATERIAL: 2000.105a, 2000.105b, 2000.106a, 2000.106b. DONOR: Department of Film. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: Spring 2000 (Item 2000.107a)
  - "What's So Funny?", January 29, 1991; SERIES: "What's So Funny?" PARTICIPANTS: Charles Silver, curator, Department of Film; Elizabeth Kendall, critic. SPONSOR: New York Women in Film SUMMARY: Charles Silver speaks about comedic strategies in the 1920's and 1930's. DATA: 2 90 Minute Standard Audio Cassettes. RELATED MATERIAL: 2000.105a, 2000.105b, 2000.106a, 2000.106b. DONOR: Department of Film. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: Spring 2000 (Item 2000.107b)
  - "Beyond Horizons in Architecture", October 3, 1991; PERSONALITY: Tadao Ando PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art. PARTICIPANTS: Stuart Wrede, director, Department of Architecture and Design, The Museum of Modern Art; Tadao Ando, architect. EXHIBITION:Tadao Ando[MoMA Exh. #1596, October 2-December 31, 1991] DATA: 2 90 Minute Standard Cassettes. SUMMARY: Wrede introduces Ando, who then speaks about his work. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: 8/1/00 (Item 2000.108a)
  - "Beyond Horizons in Architecture", October 3, 1991; PERSONALITY: Tadao Ando PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art. PARTICIPANTS: Stuart Wrede, director, Department of Architecture and Design, The Museum of Modern Art; Tadao Ando, architect. EXHIBITION:Tadao Ando[MoMA Exh. #1596, October 2-December 31, 1991] DATA: 2 90 Minute Standard Cassettes. SUMMARY: Wrede introduces Ando, who then speaks about his work. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: 8/1/00 (Item 2000.108b)
  - Untitled Panel, May 20, 1992; PARTICIPANTS: Geno Rodriquez, director of the Alternative Museum and others. SUMMARY: Multiple visiting curators speak about the varying methods of their home institutions. DATA: 1 of 4 60 Minute Standard Cassettes. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: Spring 2000; NOTE: The recording is very difficult to hear (Item 2000.109a)
  - Untitled Panel, May 20, 1992; PARTICIPANTS: Geno Rodriquez, director of the Alternative Museum and others. SUMMARY: Multiple visiting curators speak about the varying methods of their home institutions. DATA: 2 of 4 60 Minute Standard Cassettes. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: Spring 2000; NOTE: The recording is very difficult to hear (Item 2000.109b)
  - Untitled Panel, May 20, 1992; PARTICIPANTS: Geno Rodriquez, director of the Alternative Museum and others. SUMMARY: Multiple visiting curators speak about the varying methods of their home institutions. DATA: 3 of 4 60 Minute Standard Cassettes. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: Spring 2000; NOTE: The recording is very difficult to hear (Item 2000.109c)
  - Untitled Panel, May 20, 1992; PARTICIPANTS: Geno Rodriquez, director of the Alternative Museum and others. SUMMARY: Multiple visiting curators speak about the varying methods of their home institutions. DATA: 4 of 4 60 Minute Standard Cassettes. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: Spring 2000; NOTE: The recording is very difficult to hear (Item 2000.109d)
  - "High and Low Performance: David Cale", November 20, 1990; PERSONALITY: David Cale PLACE: Titus Theater 1, The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: High and Low Performance Series PARTICIPANTS: David Cale, actor and performance artist. EXHIBITION:High and Low: Modern Art and Popular Culture[MoMA Exh. #1559, October 7, 1990-January 15, 1991] DATA: 10.5 inch master reel, 7.5 IPS, 2 track. Duplicate is 10.5 inch master reel. SUMMARY: David Cale performs as part of the High and Low performance series. RELATED MATERIAL: 2001.28a, 2001.28b TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: 2000; Note: This recording is located in Long Island City, Queens. (Item 2000.110, 2000.110D)
  - "Student Gallery Talks", PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Gallery Talks. SUMMARY: Student leads a group through her lecture on Constantin Brancusi's sculptures within the Museum's permanent collection. DATA: 1 90 Minute Standard Cassette. DONOR: Department of Education. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: Spring 2000. (Item 2000.111)
  - "Contemporary Art and Its Community", March 2, 1988; PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art. SERIES: Contemporary Art in Context PARTICIPANTS: Kynaston McShine, curator, Department of Painting and Sculpture, The Museum of Modern Art; Linda Cathcart, curator; Kathy Halbreich, director, Walker Arts Center; John Neff, director, First Bank of Chicago. DATA: 1 90 Minute Standard Audio Cassette. SUMMARY: Participants discuss the character of the art world and receive questions from the audience. DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: 8/1/00 (Item 2000.112)
  - "Celebrating Yiddish", December 9, 1991; PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art EXHIBITION:Yiddish Film Between Two Worlds[MoMA Exh. #1601, November 14, 1991-January 14, 1992] DATA: 1 60 Minute Standard Audio Cassette. SUMMARY: A filmmaker reads scenes from several scripts. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: Summer 2000; NOTE: 2000.113b is blank (Item 2000.113a)
  - "Celebrating Yiddish", December 9, 1991; PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art EXHIBITION:Yiddish Film Between Two Worlds[MoMA Exh. #1601, November 14, 1991-January 14, 1992] DATA: 1 60 Minute Standard Audio Cassette. SUMMARY: A filmmaker reads scenes from several scripts. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: Summer 2000; NOTE: 2000.113b is blank (Item 2000.113b)
  - "What's So Funny?", February 5, 1991; PARTICIPANTS: Bill Irwin, actor; Lenore French, producer. SUMMARY: Participants show film clips of various comedic strategies and discuss the successes and failures of the effects. DATA: 2 90 Minute Standard Audio Cassettes. RELATED MATERIAL: 2000.123a, 2000.123b. DONOR: Department of Film. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: Spring 2000 (Item 2000.114a)
  - "What's So Funny?", February 5, 1991; SERIES: "What's So Funny?" PARTICIPANTS: Bill Irwin, actor; Lenore French, producer. SPONSOR: New York Women in Film SUMMARY: Participants show film clips of various comedic strategies and discuss the successes and failures of the effects. DATA: 2 90 Minute Standard Audio Cassettes. RELATED MATERIAL: 2000.123a, 2000.123b. DONOR: Department of Film. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: Spring 2000 (Item 2000.114b)
  - "Gowing Lecture", n.d.; PERSONALITY: Sir Lawrence Gowing PARTICIPANTS: Sir Lawrence Gowing, Czanne historian. EXHIBITION:Czanne Sketchbooks[MoMA Exh. #1479, March 10-June 5, 1988] SUMMARY: Sir Lawrence Gowing speaks about the current Czanne exhibition. DATA: 2 90 Minute Standard Audio Cassettes. DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: Spring 2000 (Item 2000.115a)
  - "Gowing Lecture", n.d.; PERSONALITY: Sir Lawrence Gowing PARTICIPANTS: Sir Lawrence Gowing, Czanne historian. EXHIBITION:Czanne Sketchbooks[MoMA Exh. #1479, March 10-June 5, 1988] SUMMARY: Sir Lawrence Gowing speaks about the current Czanne exhibition. DATA: 2 90 Minute Standard Audio Cassettes. DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: Spring 2000 (Item 2000.115b)
  - "Contemporary Art-Curators in Conversations", n.d.; PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art. PARTICIPANTS: Dale Hoyt, video curator, The Kitchen; Barbara London, assistant curator, Department of Media, The Museum of Modern Art. DATA: 1 90 Minute Standard Audio Cassette. SUMMARY: Dale Hoyt speaks about the aesthetics of bad taste and then projects video recordings that are examples of "bad taste." TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: Summer 2000; NOTE: The recording does not begin immediately (Item 2000.116)
  - "High and Low Performance: Laurie Anderson", January 8, 1991; PERSONALITY: Laurie Anderson PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art, Titus Theater 1 Theater SERIES: High and Low Performance Series PARTICIPANTS: Laurie Anderson, sound artist. EXHIBITION:High and Low: Modern Art and Popular Culture[MoMA Exh. #1559, October 7, 1990-January 15, 1991] DATA: 10.5 inch master reel, 7.5 IPS. SUMMARY: Laurie Anderson performs as part of the High and Low performance series. RELATED MATERIAL: 2001.28a, 2001.28b, 2000.118, 2000.119 DONOR: Department of Communications TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: 2000; Note: This recording is located in Long Island City, Queens. (Item 2000.117)
  - "How Alberto Became Giacometti", October 15, 2001; PLACE: Donnell Library, 20 W. 53 St., Manhattan SERIES: Giacometti Lecture Series PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Carolyn Lanchner, former Curator of Department of Painting and Sculpture, The Museum of Modern Art; Professor Reinhold Hohl; James Lord EXHIBITION:Alberto Giacometti[MoMA Exh. #1890, October 10(11), 2001-January 8, 2002] DATA: One standard 90-minute cassette, one standard 120-minute cassette SUMMARY: Lecture RELATED MATERIAL: 2001.2 - 2001.5 DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: December 2001 (Item 2001.1, 2001.1D)
  - "Giacometti's Dog", October 22, 2001; PLACE: Donnell Library, 20 W. 53 St., Manhattan SERIES: Giacometti Lecture Series PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Anne Umland, Associate Curator, Department of Painting and Sculpture, The Museum of Modern Art; Michael Brenson,New York Times art critic EXHIBITION:Alberto Giacometti[MoMA Exh. #1890, October 10(11), 2001-January 8, 2002] DATA: One standard 90-minute cassette, one standard 120-minute cassette SUMMARY: Lecture RELATED MATERIAL: 2001.1, 2001.3 - 2001.5 DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: December 2001 (Item 2001.2, 2001.2D)
  - "Perceptions at Play: Giacometti Through Contemporary Eyes", November 5, 2001; PLACE: Donnell Library, 20 W. 53 St., Manhattan SERIES: Giacometti Lecture Series PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Carolyn Lanchner, former curator, Department of Painting and Sculpture, The Museum of Modern Art; Roxana Marcoci, Curatorial Assistant, Department of Painting and Sculpture, The Museum of Modern Art EXHIBITION:Alberto Giacometti[MoMA Exh. #1890, October 10(11), 2001-January 8, 2002] DATA: One standard 90-minute cassette, one standard 120-minute cassette SUMMARY: Lecture RELATED MATERIAL: 2001.1, 2001.2, 2001.4, 2001.5 DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: December 2001 (Item 2001.3, 2001.3D)
  - "Giacometti's Grande Figure", November 16, 2001; PLACE: Donnell Library, 20 W. 53 St., Manhattan SERIES: Giacometti Lecture Series PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Anne Umland, Associate Curator, Department of Painting and Sculpture, The Museum of Modern Art; Professor Friedrich Teja Bach EXHIBITION:Alberto Giacometti[MoMA Exh. #1890, October 10(11), 2001-January 8, 2002] DATA: One standard 90-minute cassette, one standard 120-minute cassette SUMMARY: Lecture RELATED MATERIAL: 2001.1, 2001.3, 2001.5 DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: December 2001 (Item 2001.4, 2001.4D)
  - "Alberto Giacometti: An Artist Panel", November 19, 2001; PLACE: Donnell Library, 20 W. 53 St., Manhattan SERIES: Giacometti Lecture Series PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Anne Umland, Associate Curator, Department of Painting and Sculpture, The Museum of Modern Art; Richard Serra, artist; William Tucker, artist; Vija Celmins, artist; Vanessa Beecroft, artist EXHIBITION:Alberto Giacometti[MoMA Exh. #1890, October 10(11), 2001-January 8, 2002] DATA: One standard 90-minute cassette, one standard 120-minute cassette SUMMARY: Informal discussion of Giacometti's work by artists RELATED MATERIAL: 2001.1 - 2001.4 DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: December 2001 (Item 2001.5, 2001.5D)
  - "Searching for Prints: Education, Research, and Collecting on the Web, A Forum on Prints and the Internet", October 29, 2001; PLACE: Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Print Room, The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Print Week: New York PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Deborah Wye, Chief Curator, Department of Prints and Illustrated Books, The Museum of Modern Art; Introduction: Dick Solomon, President of International Fine Arts Print Dealers; Faye Hirsch; Stephen Goddard SPONSOR: International Fine Arts Print Dealers DATA: Four 90-minute Standard Audio Cassettes SUMMARY: Workshop session with lecture and discussion DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: December 2001 (Item 2001.6a, 2001.6aD)
  - "Searching for Prints: Education, Research, and Collecting on the Web, A Forum on Prints and the Internet", October 29, 2001; PLACE: Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Print Room, The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Print Week: New York PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Deborah Wye, Chief Curator, Department of Prints and Illustrated Books, The Museum of Modern Art; Introduction: Dick Solomon, President of International Fine Arts Print Dealers; Faye Hirsch; Stephen Goddard SPONSOR: International Fine Arts Print Dealers DATA: Four 90-minute Standard Audio Cassettes SUMMARY: Workshop session with lecture and discussion DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: December 2001 (Item 2001.6b, 2001.6bD)
  - Untitled, October 12, 2001; PERSONALITY: Linda Roy PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Conversations with Contemporary Artists PARTICIPANTS: Linda Roy, artist SPONSOR: The Leo and Julia Forcheimer Foundation; The Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; The Junior Associates, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One standard 90-minute cassette, one standard 120-minute cassette SUMMARY: Informal talk with the artist; first few minutes not recorded. DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: December 2001 (Item 2001.7, 2001.7D)
  - Untitled, October 19, 2001; PERSONALITY: Brad Kahlhamer PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Conversations with Contemporary Artists PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Josiana Bianchi, Public Programs Coordinator, Department of Education, The Museum of Modern Art; Brad Kahlhamer, artist SPONSOR: The Leo and Julia Forcheimer Foundation; The Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; The Junior Associates, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One standard 90-minute cassette, one standard 120-minute cassette SUMMARY: Informal talk with the artist DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: December 2001 (Item 2001.8, 2001.8D)
  - Untitled, October 26, 2001; PERSONALITY: Charles Long PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Conversations with Contemporary Artists PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Starr Figura, Assistant Curator, Department of Prints and Illustrated Books, The Museum of Modern Art; Charles Long, artist SPONSOR: The Leo and Julia Forcheimer Foundation; The Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; The Junior Associates, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One standard 90-minute cassette, one standard 120-minute cassette SUMMARY: Informal talk with the artist DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: December 2001 (Item 2001.9, 2001.9D)
  - Untitled, November 2, 2001; PERSONALITY: Joan Jonas PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Conversations with Contemporary Artists PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Sally Berger, Assistant Aurator, Department of Film and Video, The Museum of Modern Art; Joan Jonas, artist SPONSOR: The Leo and Julia Forcheimer Foundation; The Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; The Junior Associates, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One standard 90-minute cassette, one standard 120-minute cassette SUMMARY: Informal talk with the artist RELATED MATERIAL: Please see Transcripts, Folder 201. DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: December 2001 (Item 2001.10, 2001.10D)
  - Untitled, November 9, 2001; PERSONALITY: Sarah Sze PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Conversations with Contemporary Artists PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Lilian Tone, Assistant Aurator, Department of Painting and Sculpture, The Museum of Modern Art; Surah Sze, artist SPONSOR: The Leo and Julia Forcheimer Foundation; The Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; The Junior Associates, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One standard 90-minute cassette, one standard 120-minute cassette SUMMARY: Informal talk with the artist DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: December 2001 (Item 2001.11, 2001.11D)
  - Untitled, November 16, 2001; PERSONALITY: Marco Breuer PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Conversations with Contemporary Artists PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Susan Kismaric, Curator, Department of Photography, The Museum of Modern Art; Marco Breuer, artist SPONSOR: The Leo and Julia Forcheimer Foundation; The Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; The Junior Associates, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One standard 90-minute cassette, one standard 120-minute cassette SUMMARY: Informal talk with the artist DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: December 2001 (Item 2001.12, 2001.12D)
  - Untitled, April 20, 2001; PERSONALITY: Ruth Root PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Conversations with Contemporary Artists PARTICIPANTS: Ruth Root, artist SPONSOR: The Leo and Julia Forcheimer Foundation; The Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; The Junior Associates, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One standard 90-minute cassette, one standard 120-minute cassette SUMMARY: Informal talk with the artist; first few minutes not recorded. DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: July 2001 (Item 2001.13, 2001.13D)
  - Untitled, April 27, 2001; PERSONALITY: Ada Tolla and Giuseppe Lignano PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Conversations with Contemporary Artists PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Josiana Bianchi, Public Programs Coordinator, Department of Education, The Museum of Modern Art; Ada Tolla, artist; Giuseppe Lignano, artist SPONSOR: The Leo and Julia Forcheimer Foundation; The Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; The Junior Associates, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One standard 90-minute cassette, one standard 120-minute cassette SUMMARY: Informal talk with the artist DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: July 2001 (Item 2001.14, 2001.14D)
  - Untitled, May 4, 2001; PERSONALITY: Cheryl Donegan PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Conversations with Contemporary Artists PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Sally Berger, Assistant Curator, Department of Film, The Museum of Modern Art; Cheryl Donegan, artist SPONSOR: The Leo and Julia Forcheimer Foundation; The Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; The Junior Associates, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: Two standard 90-minute cassettes, two standard 120-minute cassettes SUMMARY: Informal talk with the artist and tour of galleries DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: July 2001 RELATED MATERIAL: Please see Transcripts, Folder 112; NOTE: This sound recording was preserved in Spring 2011 by the Department of Education of The Museum of Modern Art. In addition to the original, a Broadcast Wave File (BWF) archival master, a DVD audio master, and a CD-R use copy now exist. (Item 2001.15a, 2001.15aD)
  - Untitled, May 4, 2001; PERSONALITY: Cheryl Donegan PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Conversations with Contemporary Artists PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Sally Berger, Assistant Curator, Department of Film, The Museum of Modern Art; Cheryl Donegan, artist SPONSOR: The Leo and Julia Forcheimer Foundation; The Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; The Junior Associates, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: Two standard 90-minute cassettes, two standard 120-minute cassettes SUMMARY: Informal talk with the artist and tour of galleries DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: July 2001 RELATED MATERIAL: Please see Transcripts, Folder 112; NOTE: This sound recording was preserved in Spring 2011 by the Department of Education of The Museum of Modern Art. In addition to the original, a Broadcast Wave File (BWF) archival master, a DVD audio master, and a CD-R use copy now exist. (Item 2001.15b, 2001.15bD)
  - Untitled, May 11, 2001; NOTE: This recording is currently missing.; PERSONALITY: Thomas Roma PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Conversations with Contemporary Artists PARTICIPANTS: Thomas Roma, artist SPONSOR: The Leo and Julia Forcheimer Foundation; The Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; The Junior Associates, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One standard 90-minute cassette, one standard 120-minute cassette SUMMARY: Informal talk with the artist DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: July 2001 (Item 2001.16, 2001.16D)
  - Untitled, May 18, 2001; PERSONALITY: Jim Hodges PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Conversations with Contemporary Artists PARTICIPANTS: Jim Hodges, artist SPONSOR: The Leo and Julia Forcheimer Foundation; The Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; The Junior Associates, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One standard 90-minute cassette, one standard 120-minute cassette SUMMARY: Informal talk with the artist; first few minutes of introduction not recorded. DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: July 2001 (Item 2001.17, 2001.17D)
  - Untitled, April 27, 2001; PERSONALITY: Inka Essenhigh PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Conversations with Contemporary Artists PARTICIPANTS: Introduction: Starr Figura, Assistant Curator, Department of Prints and Illustrated Books, The Museum of Modern Art; Inka Essenhigh, artist SPONSOR: The Leo and Julia Forcheimer Foundation; The Contemporary Arts Council, The Museum of Modern Art; The Junior Associates, The Museum of Modern Art DATA: One standard 90-minute cassette, one standard 120-minute cassette SUMMARY: Informal talk with the artist DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: July 2001 (Item 2001.18, 2001.18D)